Guide to the Newspaper Guild of New York Records WAG.125
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Minutes, 1951-1991
  - Executive Committee (II), 1980 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee (III), 1980 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee (I), 1981 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee (II), 1981 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee (I), 1982 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee (II), 1982 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee (I), 1983 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee (II), 1983 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee, 1984 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee, 1985 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee, 1986 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee, 1987 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee, 1988 (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee, 1991 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Finance Committee, 1957-1965 (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1952-1959 (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1960-1965 (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1966-1969 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1970-1973 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1974-1978 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1979-1981 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1982-1991 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - National Wire Service Council, 1955 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Representative Assembly, 1951-1954 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - Representative Assembly, 1955 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - Representative Assembly, 1956-1957 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - Representative Assembly, 1958-1959 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - Representative Assembly, 1960 (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - Representative Assembly, 1961-1963 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Representative Assembly, 1964-1965 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Representative Assembly, 1966-1967 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Representative Assembly, 1968-1969 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Representative Assembly, 1970 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Representative Assembly, 1971 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Representative Assembly, 1972 (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - Representative Assembly, 1973 (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - Representative Assembly, 1974 (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - Representative Assembly, 1975 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Representative Assembly, 1976 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Representative Assembly, 1977 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Representative Assembly, 1978 (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Representative Assembly, 1979 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Representative Assembly (I), 1980 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Representative Assembly (II), 1980 (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - Representative Assembly, 1981 (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - Representative Assembly, 1982 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Representative Assembly, 1985; 1989 (Box 156, Folder 10)
  - Special Investigating Committee on New York Daily News Strike (I), 1973-1974 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Special Investigating Committee on New York Daily News Strike (II), 1973-1974 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Trial Board, 1979 (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Trial Board, 1980 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Trial Board, 1982; 1985 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Trial Board (I), 1991 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Trial Board (II), 1991 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - Trial Board (III), 1991 (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - Trial Board (IV), 1991 (Box 157, Folder 9)
- Series V: Shop Files, 1951-1998
  - Subseries V:A: General Shop Files, 1951-1998.
    - ACME NEA: Contracts, 1956 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Albany Times Union: Contract, 1957 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Albany Times Union: Negotiations, 1953 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Alco-Gravure: Dues, 1976; 1981 (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Alco-Gravure: Egan, Edwin R., 1981 (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Alco-Gravure: Grievances, 1978-1980 (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Alco-Gravure: National Labor Relations Board, 1981 (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Alco-Gravure: Negotiations, 1978-1980 (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Alco-Gravure: Negotiations, 1981 (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - Alco-Gravure: Organizing, 1971 (Box 158, Folder 10)
    - Alco-Gravure: Proposals and Agreement (North New Jersey Newspaper Guild), 1975-1978 (Box 158, Folder 11)
    - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Arbitrations, 1977 (Box 158, Folder 12)
    - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Contracts, 1969-1977 (Box 158, Folder 13)
    - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Correspondence, 1974 (Box 158, Folder 14)
    - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Disciplinary Charges, 1971 (Box 158, Folder 15)
    - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: General, 1978-1985 (Box 158, Folder 16)
    - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Grievances, 1969-1978 (Box 158, Folder 17)
    - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Textile (I), 1977-1979 (Box 158, Folder 18)
    - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Textile (II), 1977-1979 (Box 158, Folder 19)
    - Amalgamated Publishers: General, 1963 (Box 158, Folder 20)
    - America Illustrada: General, 1960 (Box 158, Folder 21)
    - America Oggi: General, 1988-1989 (Box 158, Folder 22)
    - American Journal of Nursing: Agreement, 1971 (Box 158, Folder 23)
    - American Journal of Nursing: Arbitrations, 1971-1972 (Box 158, Folder 24)
    - American Journal of Nursing: Arbitrations, 1975-1976 (Box 158, Folder 25)
    - American Journal of Nursing: Correspondence, 1983 (Box 158, Folder 26)
    - American Journal of Nursing: Contracts, 1973-1979 (Box 158, Folder 27)
    - American Journal of Nursing: Contracts, 1982 (Box 158, Folder 28)
    - American Journal of Nursing: Contracts, 1985-1988 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - American Journal of Nursing: Dues, 1991 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - American Journal of Nursing: General, 1971-1972; 1989 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - American Journal of Nursing: Grievances, 1972-1980 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - American Journal of Nursing: Grievances, 1981-1987 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - American Journal of Nursing: Membership Applications, 1972 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - American Journal of Nursing: Minutes, 1972 (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - American Journal of Nursing: Narod, Susan, 1980 (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - American Journal of Nursing: Negotiations, 1973 (Box 159, Folder 9)
    - American Journal of Nursing: Negotiations, 1979; 1982-1984 (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - American Journal of Nursing: Organizing, 1972 (Box 159, Folder 11)
    - American Journal of Nursing: Personnel, 1976 (Box 159, Folder 12)
    - American Journal of Nursing: Steers, Tom, 1986 (Box 159, Folder 13)
    - American Journal of Nursing: Yampolsky, Selma, 1980 (Box 159, Folder 14)
    - American Republican, Inc.: Contract, 1982-1984 (Box 159, Folder 15)
    - American Weekly: Arbitrations, 1951-1954; 1961 (Box 159, Folder 16)
    - American Weekly: Contracts, 1951-1962 (Box 159, Folder 17)
    - American Weekly: General, 1951 (Box 159, Folder 18)
    - American Weekly: Grievances, 1952; 1957-1963 (Box 159, Folder 19)
    - American Weekly: Negotiations, 1952-1960 (Box 159, Folder 20)
    - Amsterdam News: Advertising, 1967 (Box 159, Folder 21)
    - Amsterdam News: Advertising Solicitors, 1968-1969 (Box 159, Folder 22)
    - Amsterdam News: Advertising Solicitors, 1975-1977 (Box 159, Folder 23)
    - Amsterdam News: Arbitrations, 1968-1973 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Amsterdam News: Arbitrations, 1980 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Amsterdam News: Arbitrations, 1983 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Amsterdam News: Arbitrations, 1983 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Amsterdam News: Arbitrations, 1983 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Amsterdam News: Arbitrations, 1983 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Amsterdam News: City Desk (Shop Paper), 1969-1974 (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Amsterdam News: Civilian Police Complaint, 1983 (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - Amsterdam News: Commission Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - Amsterdam News: Contracts, 1957-1958 (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - Amsterdam News: Contracts, 1966-1969 (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - Amsterdam News: Contracts, 1976-1986 (Box 160, Folder 12)
    - Amsterdam News: Contracts, 1987-1995 (Box 160, Folder 13)
    - Amsterdam News: Corporate Structure, 1983 (Box 160, Folder 14)
    - Amsterdam News: Correspondence, 1968-1977 (Box 160, Folder 15)
    - Amsterdam News: Dismissals, 1951-1953 (Box 160, Folder 16)
    - Amsterdam News: Dismissals, 1964-1965 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Amsterdam News: Dismissals, 1967-1979 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Amsterdam News: Dismissals, 1983 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Amsterdam News: Disputes, 1955; 1971; 1983 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Amsterdam News: Egan, Edwin R., 1982 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Amsterdam News: Environmental Health Project, 1980 (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Amsterdam News: Dues, 1983; 1991 (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Amsterdam News: Exemptions, 1974; 1983 (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - Amsterdam News: Fisdell, Harry (Pension Fund Audit), 1975 (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - Amsterdam News: General, 1968-1988 (Box 161, Folder 10)
    - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1951-1955 (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1956-1958 (Box 161, Folder 12)
    - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1959-1960 (Box 161, Folder 13)
    - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1961-1963 (Box 161, Folder 14)
    - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1964-1965 (Box 161, Folder 15)
    - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1966-1967 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1968 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1969 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1970 (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1971 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1972 (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1973 (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1974 (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1976-1977 (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1978-1979 (Box 162, Folder 10)
    - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1980 (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1981 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1982-1985 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Amsterdam News: Hairston, Thomas (Unit Chairman), 1970 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Amsterdam News: Health and Welfare Fund, 1973-1976 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Amsterdam News: Job Descriptions, 1971-1975 (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Amsterdam News: Job Evaluations, 1967-1968 (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Amsterdam News: Nash, Malcolm (Reclassification), 1961 (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - Amsterdam News: National Labor Relations Board (Cases), 1982-1983 (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - Amsterdam News: National Labor Relations Board (Union Security Election), 1951 (Box 163, Folder 9)
    - Amsterdam News: Negotiations, 1951-1952 (Box 163, Folder 10)
    - Amsterdam News: Negotiations, 1953-1955 (Box 163, Folder 11)
    - Amsterdam News: Negotiations, 1960 (Box 163, Folder 12)
    - Amsterdam News: Negotiations, 1962 (Box 163, Folder 13)
    - Amsterdam News: Negotiations, 1964 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Amsterdam News: Negotiations, 1966 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Amsterdam News: Negotiations (I), 1968 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Amsterdam News: Negotiations (II), 1968 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Amsterdam News: Negotiations, 1971 (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Amsterdam News: Negotiations, 1972 (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Amsterdam News: Negotiations, 1974 (Box 164, Folder 7)
    - Amsterdam News: Negotiations, 1975 (Box 164, Folder 8)
    - Amsterdam News: Negotiations, 1977-1979 (Box 164, Folder 9)
    - Amsterdam News: Negotiations, 1980-1982 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Amsterdam News: Negotiations, 1983 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Amsterdam News: Negotiations, 1984 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Amsterdam News: O'Jay, Eddie, 1983 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Amsterdam News: Pettiford, Johnson, and Jones (Monies Due), 1960 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Amsterdam News: Payroll Information, 1980-1981 (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Amsterdam News: Personnel, 1961-1968 (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Amsterdam News: Personnel, 1969-1982 (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - Amsterdam News: Poindexter, Herbert (Arbitrations Award), 1963-1964 (Box 165, Folder 9)
    - Amsterdam News: Proposals, 1971 (Box 165, Folder 10)
    - Amsterdam News: Publicity, 1983 (Box 165, Folder 11)
    - Amsterdam News: Reinstatements, 1953, 1963 (Box 165, Folder 12)
    - Amsterdam News: Rowe, James (Arbitrations), 1976 (Box 165, Folder 13)
    - Amsterdam News: Stock Offer, 1971 (Box 165, Folder 14)
    - Amsterdam News: Strike, 1968 (Box 165, Folder 15)
    - Amsterdam News: Strike, 1983 (Box 165, Folder 16)
    - Amsterdam News: Tatum, Strict Compliance Letter, 1983 (Box 165, Folder 17)
    - Amsterdam News: Unit Elections, 1974 (Box 165, Folder 18)
    - Amsterdam News: Vann. Robert (Attorney), 1982-1983 (Box 165, Folder 19)
    - Amsterdam News: Young, Nathaniel and Ed Warner (Arbitrations), 1967 (Box 165, Folder 20)
    - Antiques Magazine (Straight Enterprises, Inc.): Contracts, 1973-1983 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Antiques Magazine: Negotiations, 1979 (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - ANSA News Agency: Contract, 1970-1991 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - ANSA News Agency: Grievances, 1972-1978 (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - ANSA News Agency: Grievances, 1983-1992 (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - ANSA News Agency: Negotiations, 1974-1981 (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - ANSA News Agency: Pension Plan and Trust, 1976 (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - ANSA News Agency: Transfers (Varela, Carlos and Aleman, Adolfo), 1980-1982 (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - Armstrong Daily: Organizing, 1971 (Box 166, Folder 9)
    - Associated Press: General, 1951 (Box 166, Folder 10)
    - Associated Press: Grievances, 1951-1954 (Box 166, Folder 11)
    - Associated Press: Grievances, 1955-1958 (Box 166, Folder 12)
    - Associated Press: Negotiations, 1951-1956; 1966 (Box 166, Folder 13)
    - Associated Press: Negotiation Bulletins, 1953-1954 (Box 166, Folder 14)
    - Associated Press: Strike, 1969 (Box 166, Folder 14a)
    - Associated Press: Unit Elections, 1956 (Box 166, Folder 15)
    - Associated Press: Wage Reopener, 1954 (Box 166, Folder 16)
    - At Time, Inc.: On Time, 1976 (Box 166, Folder 17)
    - Atlantis: Contracts, 1952-1956 (Box 166, Folder 18)
    - Atlantis: Contracts, 1958-1964 (Box 166, Folder 19)
    - Atlantis: Grievances, 1952-1956 (Box 166, Folder 20)
    - Atlantis: Grievances, 1957-1963 (Box 166, Folder 21)
    - Atlantis: Grievances, 1964-1973 (Box 166, Folder 22)
    - Atlantis: National Labor Relations Board Elections and Organizing, 1951-1952 (Box 166, Folder 23)
    - Atlantis: Negotiations, 1952-1953 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Atlantis: Negotiations, 1956-1962 (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - Atlantis: Negotiations, 1966-1972 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Atlantis: Personnel, 1967-1973 (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Atlantis: Reopening, 1955 (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Atlantis: Strike, 1953 (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Atlantis: Yoannou, Thomas (Arbitrations), 1962 (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Atlas Publishing Company: Organizing, 1953 (Box 167, Folder 8)
    - Aufbau: Contracts, 1951-1960 (Box 167, Folder 9)
    - Aufbau: Contracts, 1963-1977 (Box 167, Folder 10)
    - Aufbau: Correspondence, 1962 (Box 167, Folder 11)
    - Aufbau: Deegan, John E. (Executive Vice-President), 1972 (Box 167, Folder 12)
    - Aufbau: Grievances, 1951-1977 (Box 167, Folder 13)
    - Aufbau: Negotiations, 1951-1959 (Box 167, Folder 14)
    - Australian Associated Press: Grievances, 1963 (Box 167, Folder 15)
    - Australian Associated Press: Negotiations, 1962 (Box 167, Folder 16)
    - Bell Syndicate: Contracts, 1951-1957 (Box 167, Folder 17)
    - Bell Syndicate: Contracts, 1951-1953 (Box 167, Folder 18)
    - Bell Syndicate: Contracts, 1958-1971 (Box 167, Folder 19)
    - Bell Syndicate: General, 1951-1972 (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Bell Syndicate: Grievances, 1955-1959 (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Bell Syndicate: Grievances, 1960-1963 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Bell Syndicate: Grievances, 1964-1971 (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - Bell Syndicate: Grievances, 1971-1972 (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Bell Syndicate: Minutes, 1951-1953 (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Bell Syndicate: Negotiations, 1951-1954 (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - Bell Syndicate: Negotiations, 1958-1961 (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - Bell Syndicate: Negotiations (Bell McClure), 1964-1969 (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - Bell Syndicate: Organizational, 1969 (Box 168, Folder 10)
    - Bell Syndicate: Personnel, 1953; 1961-1964 (Box 168, Folder 11)
    - Berlitz: Organizing, 1978 (Box 168, Folder 12)
    - Billboard: Arbitrations, 1964 (Box 168, Folder 13)
    - Billboard: Contracts, 1951-1964 (Box 168, Folder 14)
    - Billboard: General, 1951-1965 (Box 168, Folder 15)
    - Billboard: Grievances, 1964 (Box 168, Folder 16)
    - Billboard: Minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 168, Folder 17)
    - Billboard: Negotiations, 1952-1958 (Box 168, Folder 18)
    - Billboard: Negotiations, 1960-1963 (Box 168, Folder 19)
    - Bridgeport Telegram: Organizing, 1976 (Box 168, Folder 20)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Arbitrations, 1951-1957 (Box 168, Folder 21)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Arbitrations, 1958-1960 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Benefits (I), 1955-1956 (Box 169, Folder 2)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Benefits (II), 1955-1956 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Clippings, 1955 (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Contracts, 1951-1959 (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Correspondence (Auction), 1958 (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Correspondence (Employee Authorization), 1955 (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Correspondence (Employee Questionnaire), 1955 (Box 169, Folder 8)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Correspondence (Employee Statements), 1955 (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Correspondence (Honorable Withdrawal Cards), 1955 (Box 169, Folder 10)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Correspondence (Job Survey) (I), undated (Box 169, Folder 11)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Correspondence (Job Survey) (II), undated (Box 169, Folder 12)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Correspondence (Job Survey) (III), undated (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Correspondence (Personnel), 1955 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Correspondence (Severance Pay Disbursements) (I), 1960-1964 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Correspondence (Severance Pay Disbursements) (II), 1960-1964 (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Correspondence (Strike), 1954-1955 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Correspondence (Strike), 1955-1956 (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Eagle Reporter (Shop Paper), 1952-1955 (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Employment Records, 1955 (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: General, 1951-1959 (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: General, 1960-1963 (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Grievances, 1952-1963 (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Negotiations, 1951-1955 (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Negotiations, 1956-1960 (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Organizing, 1963 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Placement Service, 1955 (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Reclassifications, 1952 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Reopening, 1953-1954 (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Settlement, 1960 (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Smith, Herbert (Dismissal), 1965 (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Strike (Picket Time Schedules), 1955 (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Strike Benefits, 1955 (Box 171, Folder 9)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Strike Benefits (Applications), 1955 (Box 171, Folder 10)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Strike Bulletins, 1955 (Box 171, Folder 11)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Strike Contributions (I), 1955 (Box 171, Folder 12)
    - Brooklyn Eagle: Strike Contributions (II), 1955 (Box 171, Folder 13)
    - Brooklyn Today, 1972-1973 (Box 171, Folder 14)
    - Catholic News: Organizing, 1964 (Box 171, Folder 15)
    - Chanry Publications: Weekender, 1989 (Box 171, Folder 16)
    - Chicago Tribune: Contracts, 1981-1984 (Box 171, Folder 17)
    - Chicago Tribune: Grievance, 1983 (Box 171, Folder 18)
    - Chicago Tribune: Strike, 1985 (Box 171, Folder 19)
    - CMP Publications: Organizing, 1982 (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Columbia Broadcasting System (CBS), 1951-1963 (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Commonweal: Grievances, 1951-1954 (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - Comtelburo: Contracts, 1957-1961 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Comtelburo: Grievances, 1952-1959 (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Comtelburo: Grievances, 1960-1963 (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Comtelburo: Grievances, 1964-1966 (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - Comtelburo: Negotiations, 1951-1961 (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - Comtelburo: Negotiations, 1963 (Box 172, Folder 9)
    - Comtelburo: Negotiations, 1965 (Box 172, Folder 10)
    - Comtelburo: Reopening, 1952 (Box 172, Folder 11)
    - Conde Nast: Organizing, 1982 (Box 172, Folder 12)
    - Consumers Union: Arbitrations, 1973-1975 (Box 172, Folder 13)
    - Consumers Union: Arbitrations, 1976 (Box 172, Folder 14)
    - Consumers Union: Arbitrations (I), 1977 (Box 172, Folder 15)
    - Consumers Union: Arbitrations (II), 1977 (Box 172, Folder 16)
    - Consumers Union: Arbitrations, 1978-1980 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Consumers Union: Arbitrations, 1981 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Consumers Union: Arbitrations, 1982 (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Consumers Union: Arbitrations, 1983-1989 (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - Consumers Union: Arbitrations (Portable Window Fan Testing), 1960-1972 (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - Consumers Union: Arbitrations (Portable Window Fan Testing), 1973-1974 (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - Consumers Union: Arbitrations (Portable Window Fan Testing), 1975-1976 (Box 173, Folder 7)
    - Consumers Union: Automation, 1977 (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - Consumers Union: Beauchamp, Alex (Unit Chairman), 1977 (Box 173, Folder 9)
    - Consumers Union: Boycott, 1987 (Box 173, Folder 10)
    - Consumers Union: Conflict of Interest Guidelines, 1980 (Box 173, Folder 11)
    - Consumers Union: Consumers Union v. James Boyd and Gordon Hard, 1987 (Box 173, Folder 12)
    - Consumers Union: Contract, 1957-1962 (Box 173, Folder 13)
    - Consumers Union: Contract, 1963-1964 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Consumers Union: Contract, 1965 (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - Consumers Union: Contract, 1966 (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Consumers Union: Contract, 1967 (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Consumers Union: Contract, 1968-1969 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Consumers Union: Contract, 1972-1975 (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - Consumers Union: Contract, 1978-1981 (Box 174, Folder 7)
    - Consumers Union: Corrections and Retractions (Clippings), 1975 (Box 174, Folder 8)
    - Consumers Union: Dismissals, 1964-1976 (Box 174, Folder 9)
    - Consumers Union: Dismissals, 1981-1982 (Box 174, Folder 10)
    - Consumers Union: Elections, 1969-1975; 1992; 1998 (Box 174, Folder 11)
    - Consumers Union: Exemptions, 1980-1984 (Box 174, Folder 12)
    - Consumers Union: Finances, 1975 (Box 174, Folder 13)
    - Consumers Union: General, 1951-1955 (Box 174, Folder 14)
    - Consumers Union: General, 1956-1964 (Box 174, Folder 15)
    - Consumers Union: General, 1966 (Box 174, Folder 16)
    - Consumers Union: General, 1969 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Consumers Union: General, 1970-1972 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Consumers Union: General, 1973 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Consumers Union: General, 1974-1977 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Consumers Union: General, 1978-1979 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Consumers Union: General, 1980-1982 (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Consumers Union: General, 1983-1986 (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Consumers Union: General, 1987-1989 (Box 175, Folder 8)
    - Consumers Union: Grievance Applications, 1969-1983 (Box 175, Folder 9)
    - Consumers Union: Grievances, 1952-1959 (Box 175, Folder 10)
    - Consumers Union: Grievances, 1960-1961 (Box 175, Folder 11)
    - Consumers Union: Grievances, 1962-1963 (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Consumers Union: Grievances, 1964 (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - Consumers Union: Grievances, 1965 (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - Consumers Union: Grievances, 1967 (Box 176, Folder 4)